VINCENT TSUN

#2904 – 2225 Holdom Ave., Burnaby, BC, V5B 0A1
778.859.9311 | vincenttsun@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/vincent-tsun

PROFILE

Fourth-year Commerce student specializing in Finance with excellent leadership abilities from student council executive experiences. Constantly exploring different possibilities for personal growth. Strongly believes in the importance of social responsibility. Eager for an opportunity to learn from the practical application of quantitative data analysis.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Commerce, UBC Sauder School of Business

Graduation Date: May 2022

- Specialization: Finance
- Key courses: Risk Management and Financial Engineering, Corporate Finance, Investment Theory

University Transfer Program, Alexander College

Sep 2016 - May 2018

- Received Honour Roll twice
- Service Award: Outstanding services as the President of Alexander College Student Association

WORK EXPERIENCE

Student Worker, Alexander College Library

Dec 2017 – Apr 2018

- Provided exceptional customer service for a diverse range of library patrons, increasing patron satisfaction
- Processed customer fines, managed basic patron requests, and kept library shelves and printed materials organized
- Organized workshops and offered regular technical supports to library patrons on the utilization of various academic resources

LEADERSHIP AND VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Marketing Director, UBC Finance Association, UBC

Jan 2019 – April 2019

- Optimized awareness of the association by managing our official social media accounts
- Improved brand image by redesigning the official website
- Maintained attention through bi-weekly newsletters

Student Representative, Green Committee, Alexander College

Nov 2017 – Apr 2018

- Solved the need for a new garbage disposal system through surveying staff and students, analyzing results, and developing several feasible solutions
- Raised \$2,400 for Multi-Stream Waste Sorting Bins Project
- Raised social awareness about concerning environmental issues through distributing information pamphlets, developing online advertisement, and facilitating on-campus interactive activities

President, Alexander College Student Association, Alexander College

May 2017 – Apr 2018

- Increased participating members by more than 100%, through developing on-campus interactive promotions and social media advertising
- Enhanced overall decisiveness and productiveness through developing an effective hierarchy system for student association and coordinated it under an efficiency-improving voting system
- Promoted sustainability by managing recycling projects in conjunction with Green Committee

PERSONAL AND SCHOOL PROJECTS

Pricing model for callable structured notes (R)

• Based on RBC Callable Yield Canadian Utilities Securities (CAD), Series 273. Prices evaluated with Monte Carlo simulation, written in R-script.

Canadian Cannabis industry analysis 2020 (Tableau)

 A complete analysis on the Canadian cannabis industry using data on cannabis supply and consumption, consumer base, dispensary locations, and consumer product preferences to evaluate the future trends of cannabis products

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

Languages: Fluent in English, Cantonese, and Mandarin

Programming languages: Various experience with Python and R.

Other skills: Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite (Word, PowerPoint, and Excel), data visualization software like Tableau and Power BI, and graphic design platform Canva.

Interests: Piano, ukulele, photography, travelling, gaming